BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Bakery Workers - Baltimore, MD, 1931-1932 (Box 30, Folder 70)
- Plumbers and Gasfitters - Baltimore, MD, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 71)
- Typographical - Baltimore, MD, 1930-1932 (Box 30, Folder 72)
- Cement Finishers - Baltimore, MD, 1929-1932 (Box 30, Folder 73)
- Sprinkler Fitters - Baltimore, MD, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 74)
- Bridge Structural and Iron Workers - Baltimore, MD, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 75)
- Dye Workers - New Jersey (Box 30, Folder 76)
- Fur Workers - Chicago, IL (Box 30, Folder 77)
- Marine Firemen - Chicago, IL, 1928-1932 (Box 30, Folder 78)
- RR Yardmen - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 79)
- Brewers - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 80)
- Electrical Workers - Chicago, IL, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 81)
- Cooks - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 82)
- Mechanics - Chicago, IL (Box 30, Folder 83)
- Clothing Workers - Chicago, IL, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 84)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees - Chicago, IL, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 85)
- Musicians - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 86)
- Patternmakers - Chicago, IL, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 87)
- Blacksmiths - Chicago, IL, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 88)
- Painters - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 89)
- Lithographers - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 90)
- Boot and Shoe Workers - Chicago, IL, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 91)
- Telegraphers - Chicago, IL, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 92)
- Retail Clerks - Chicago, IL, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 93)
- Bill Posters - Chicago, IL, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 94)
- Engineers - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 95)
- Carpenters - Chicago, IL, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 96)
- Brickmakers - Chicago, IL, 1930-1933 (Box 30, Folder 97)
- Gardeners - Chicago, IL, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 98)
- Dairy Employees - Chicago, IL, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 99)
- Window Dressers - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 100)
- Meat Cutters - Chicago, IL, 1929-1932 (Box 30, Folder 101)
- Stage Employees - Chicago, IL, 1929-1931 (Box 30, Folder 102)
- Egg Inspectors - Chicago, IL, 1931-1932 (Box 30, Folder 103)
- Icemen - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 104)
- Cameramen - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 105)
- Drug Clerks - Chicago, IL, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 106)
- Upholsterers - Chicago, IL, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 107)
- Molders - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 108)
- Broom Makers - Chicago, IL, 1929-1932 (Box 30, Folder 109)
- Elevator Operators - Chicago, IL, 1929-1932 (Box 30, Folder 110)
- Asphalt Workers - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 111)
- Bookbinders - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 112)
- Machinists - Chicago, IL, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 113)
- Gas Workers - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 114)
- Metal Workers - Chicago, IL, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 115)
- Janitors - Chicago, IL, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 116)
- Firemen - Miami, FL, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Firemen - Jacksonville, FL, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Broom and Whisk Workers - Cleveland, OH, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Elevator Constructors - Cleveland, OH, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Asbestos Workers - Cleveland, OH, 1924-1932 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Roofers - Cleveland, OH, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Granite Cutters - Cleveland, OH, 1929-1931 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Painters - Cleveland, OH, 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  1932, 1933
- Bakers - Cleveland, OH, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Barbers - Cleveland, OH, 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Pressmen - Cleveland, OH, 1929-1933 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Marine Engineers - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Sheet Metal Workers - Cleveland, OH, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Steam Fitters - Cleveland, OH, 1927-1929 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Photo Engravers - Cleveland, OH, 1925-1934 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  1925, 1929-1934
- Electrotypers - Cleveland, OH, 1928-1931 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Plasterers - Cleveland, OH, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Plumbers - Cleveland, OH, 1927-1932 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Bridge Structural and Iron Workers - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Carpenters - Cleveland, OH, 1928-1932 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Furniture Handlers - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Waiters - Cleveland, OH, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Engineers - Cleveland, OH, 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Electrical Workers - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Bottlemakers - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Clothing Workers - Cleveland, OH, 1924-1932 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Marine Firemen - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Upholsterers - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Model Makers - Cleveland, OH, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Engineers - Cleveland, OH, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Molders - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Stage Employees - Cleveland, OH, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Patternmakers - Cleveland, OH, 1926-1932 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Boilermakers - Cleveland, OH, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Mailers - Cleveland, OH, 1929-1931 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Musicians - Denver, CO, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Policemen - Dallas, TX, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Firemen - Detroit, MI, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- Boilermakers - New Orleans, LA, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Machinists - New Orleans, LA, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Metal Trades - New Orleans, LA, 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Iron Molders - New Orleans, LA, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Foundry Workers - New Orleans, LA, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- Engineers - New Orleans, LA, 1921-1932 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- Meat Cutters - New Orleans, LA, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- Tailors - New Orleans, LA, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- Stage Employees - New Orleans, LA, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- Musicians - New Orleans, LA, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- Scalemen - New Orleans, LA, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- Longshoremen - New Orleans, LA, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- Cotton Rollers - New Orleans, LA, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 51)
- Waiters - New Orleans, LA, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- Coffee Workers - New Orleans, LA, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 53)
- Boiler Workers - Seattle, WA, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 54)
- Meat Cutters - Seattle, WA, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 55)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees - Seattle, WA, 1929-1930 (Box 31, Folder 56)
- Tailors - Seattle, WA, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 57)
- Bill Posters - Seattle, WA, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 58)
- Cleaners - Seattle, WA, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 59)
- Retail Clerks - Seattle, WA, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 60)
- Stenographers - Seattle, WA, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 61)
- Millmen - Seattle, WA, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 62)
- Dredge Workers - Seattle, WA, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 63)
- Newsboys - Seattle, WA, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 64)
- Cooks - Seattle, WA, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 65)
- Waiters - Seattle, WA, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 66)
  1929, 1932
- Musicians - Seattle, WA, 1928-1932 (Box 31, Folder 67)
- Electrical Workers - Seattle, WA, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 68)
- Mechanics - Seattle, WA, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 69)
- Marine Engineers - Seattle, WA, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 70)
- Seamen - Seattle, WA, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 71)
- Clothing Workers - New York, NY, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 72)
- Weighers - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 73)
- Pocketbook Workers - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 74)
- Glass Workers - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 75)
- Musicians - New York, NY, 1928-1932 (Box 31, Folder 76)
- Stage Employees - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 77)
- Butchers - New York, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 78)
- Paving Cutters - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 79)
- Iron and Bronze Workers - New York, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 31, Folder 80)
- Compressed Air Workers - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 81)
- Fur Workers - New York, NY, 1929-1933 (Box 31, Folder 82)
- Waiters - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 83)
- Marine Divers - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 84)
- Lamp Workers - New York, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 85)
- Auto Workers - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 86)
- Lithographers - New York, NY, 1926-1932 (Box 31, Folder 87)
- Pavers - New York, NY, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 88)
- Stenographers - New York, NY, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 89)
- Upholsterers - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 90)
- Paperhangers - New York, NY, 1928-1932 (Box 31, Folder 91)
- Hatters - New York, NY, 1929-1933 (Box 31, Folder 92)
- Hosiery Manufacturers - New York, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 93)
- Riggers - New York, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 94)
- Mailers - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 95)
- Boot and Shoe Workers - New York, NY, 1929-1933 (Box 31, Folder 96)
- Paper Handlers - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 97)
- Flooring Workers - New York, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 98)
- Neckwear Cutters - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 99)
- Cooks - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 100)
- Firemen - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 101)
- Window Cleaners - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 102)
- Lead Burners - New York, NY, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 103)
- Special Officers - New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 104)
- Marble Polishers - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 105)
- Machinery Movers - New York, NY, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 106)
- Carpenters - New York, NY, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 107)
- Molders - St. Louis, MO, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 108)
- Boilermakers - St. Louis, MO, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 109)
- Foundry Employees - St. Louis, MO, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 110)
- Cigar Makers - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1931 (Box 31, Folder 111)
  1930, 1931
- Beverage Workers - St. Louis, MO, 1926-1932 (Box 31, Folder 112)
- Boot and Shoe Workers - St. Louis, MO, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 113)
- Riggers - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 114)
- Telegraphers - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1931 (Box 31, Folder 115)
- Barbers - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 116)
- Patternmakers - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 117)
- Metal Trades - St. Louis, MO, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 118)
- Mailers - St. Louis, MO, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 119)
- Cooks - St. Louis, MO, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 120)
- Meat Cutters - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 121)
- Musicians - St. Louis, MO, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 122)
- Jewelers - St. Louis, MO, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 123)
- Tailors - St. Louis, MO, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 124)
- Neckwear Cutters - St. Louis, MO, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 125)
- Typists - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 126)
- RR Employees - St. Louis, MO, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 127)
- Marble Polishers - St. Louis, MO, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 128)
- Waiters - St. Louis, MO, 1929-1932 (Box 31, Folder 129)
- Stores - Roslyn, Wash., 1924 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Stores - Roslyn, WA, 1924-1927 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Agreement effective 01/01/1924 and expires on 06/01/1927. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Roslyn, WA.
    Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
- Grocery & Market Drivers - Chicago, IL, Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Grocery and Market Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1917-1920 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 05/01/1917 and expires on 05/01/1920. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
- Grocery Teamsters - NYC, 1917-1919 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Grocery Teamsters - New York, NY, 1917-1918 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 04/01/1917 and expires on 04/01/1918. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New York, NY.
  - Item 2: Grocery Teamsters - New York, NY, 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 03/20/1918 and expires on 03/15/1919. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New York, NY.
  - Item 3: Grocery Teamsters - New York, NY, 1919-1920 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 05/15/1919 and expires on 05/15/1920. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New York, NY.
- Grocery Teamsters - Cleveland, OH, 1921; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Grocery Teamsters - Cleveland, OH, 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Agreement effective 06/01/1921 and expires on 06/01/1922. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Cleveland, OH.
- Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1913-1920 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1913-1914 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 01/01/1913 and expires on 01/01/1914. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 2: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1915-1917 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 05/01/1915 and expires on 05/15/1917. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 3: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1915-1917 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 05/01/1915 and expires on 05/01/1917. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 4: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1917-1918 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 05/15/1917 and expires on 11/30/1918. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 5: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1917-1918 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 12/01/1918 and expires on 12/01/1919. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 7: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 12/01/1918 and expires on 09/15/1919. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 8: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1919-1921 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 09/15/1919 and expires on 05/15/1921. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 9: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1919-1921 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1925 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 06/15/1920 and expires on 05/15/1925. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 11: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1926 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 06/15/1920 and expires on 05/15/1926. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 12: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1928 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 06/15/1920 and expires on 05/15/1928. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 13: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1925 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 06/15/1920 and expires on 06/15/1921. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
  - Item 15: Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 11/01/1923 and expires on 11/01/1924. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Fransisco, CA.
- Tea + Coffee Drives - Chicago, IL (1913, 1916, 1919, 1926), 1913-1926 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Tea and Coffee Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1913-1914 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 02/01/1913 and expires on 02/01/1914. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Item 3: Tea and Coffee Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1915-1916 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 02/01/1915 and expires on 02/01/1916. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Item 4: Tea and Coffee Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 02/01/1916 and expires on 05/15/1919. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Item 5: Tea and Coffee Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1919-1920 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 02/01/1919 and expires on 02/01/1920. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Item 6: Tea and Coffee Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1926-1928 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 03/01/1926 and expires on 03/01/1928. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
- Grocery Clerks - San Francisco, CA, 1929; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Grocery Clerks - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Agreement effective 10/01/1920 and expires on 10/01/1921. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Francisco, CA.
  - Item 2: Grocery Clerks - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1933 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Agreement effective 10/01/1920 and expires on 05/15/1933. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Francisco, CA.
  - Item 3: Grocery Clerks - San Francisco, CA, 1920-1933 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Retail Clerks - Chicago, IL, 1928; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Retail Clerks - Chicago, IL, 1928-1929 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Agreement effective 04/01/1928 and expires on 03/31/1929. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Item 2: Retail Clerks - Chicago, IL, 1930-1931 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Agreement effective 04/01/1930 and expires on 03/31/1931. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
- Drug Clerks - Chicago, IL, 1931; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Drug Clerks - Chicago, IL, 1929-1928 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Agreement effective 05/15/1929 and expires on 06/01/1928. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
- Retail Workers - Seattle, WA, 1931-1932 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Retail Clerks - Seattle, WA, 1932-1933 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Agreement effective 05/15/1932 and expires on 05/15/1933. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Seattle, WA.
- Pharmacists - Stockton, CA, 1923; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Pharmacists - San Francisco, CA, 1923; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Market Truckmen - NYC, 1927; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Retail Clerks - Retail Clerks Int'l. Protective Assoc., 1918; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Pharmacists - American Registered Pharmacists, 1922; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Hardware Dealers - Brooklyn, NY, 1926; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Retail Clerks - Denver, CO, 1907; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 17)
- R.C.I.P.A. employees - National (n.d.), Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Gas workers - Chicago, IL, 1932; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Teachers - American Fed. Of Teachers, 1922; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 32, Folder 20)